<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="QA_answer_1">Ans: The new ZUK model</string>
    <string name="QA_answer_10">Ans: The timer will start upon activation. For general packages, 24 hours is considered one day. For example, if you activate a 2-day package at 16:00 on January 1, your package will expire on 16:00 on January 3.</string>
    <string name="QA_answer_11">Ans: Z-Roaming uses a virtual SIM card; as with physical SIM cards, there must be network coverage in your current region. All Z-Roaming packages are currently region-specific. Hence, you will need to check that your destination is within one of the supported regions. If you were unsuccessful in activating the service in a supported region, it is usually due to poor signal or absence of operator coverage in that region. Under such circumstances, you can try activating the service at another location.</string>
    <string name="QA_answer_12">Ans: The Z-Roaming service will disable the physical SIM card in one card slot. Hence, for single SIM mobile phones, physical SIM cards can no longer be used. For dual SIM mobile phones, the card in the other card slot can be used normally. Should you need to use the physical SIM card, you will need to close the Z-Roaming service.</string>
    <string name="QA_answer_13">Ans: No. Z-Roaming uses virtual SIM card technology, which will have absolutely no effect on the physical SIM card in your mobile phone. It will not incur any data usage and will not damage the physical SIM card.</string>
    <string name="QA_answer_14">Ans: You may do so if it is within the validity period of the order and if you have not activated your order. Upon approval, you will receive the refund in the account through which you made your payment within 7 working days. Should you fail to activate your order within its validity period and fail to request for a refund, the service will become invalid and no refund will be made. Generally, refund requests cannot be made for activated orders.</string>
    <string name="QA_answer_15">Ans: Should you encounter any problem while using our services, you can add our WeChat public number (红茶漫游) to submit your feedback on your problem.</string>
    <string name="QA_answer_2">Ans: It will be initially available in Asian countries. Subsequently, beta services will be launched in Europe and the United States, and our coverage will expand to close to 100 countries. You can find the currently supported countries and regions, as well as the respective package prices on our service list.</string>
    <string name="QA_answer_3">Ans: Currently, only data network services are supported. Voice mails and SMS services will be respectively launched at later dates.</string>
    <string name="QA_answer_4">Ans: We recommend that you make your purchase while connected to a domestic network or a Wi-Fi network overseas.</string>
    <string name="QA_answer_5">Ans: Currently, Z-Roaming supports payment through WeChat Pay and Alipay. You can make your payments through either of the above if you have a WeChat or Alipay account. More payment options will be available in the future.</string>
    <string name="QA_answer_6">Ans: After purchasing a service, you will need to activate it before it can be used. The timer will start upon activation, and no request for refund will be entertained thereafter. (Network connection not required for activation) We recommend that you activate your order after reaching your of destination.</string>
    <string name="QA_answer_7">Ans: In general, 3G network speed will be supported. However, some countries may have 2G or 4G networks, hence, actual speeds may vary between operators in different regions.</string>
    <string name="QA_answer_8">Ans: It will take around 2-4 minutes to activate this service. After a signal is detected on your phone, it may take a few minutes for you to access the network.</string>
    <string name="QA_answer_9">Ans: Hotspot sharing is supported in most countries. If hotspot sharing is not supported or is limited in number for packages specific to a country, these will be stated clearly in our package details.</string>
    <string name="QA_question_1">1. What are the models that currently support Z-Roaming?</string>
    <string name="QA_question_10">10. When is the start time of my Z-Roaming service?</string>
    <string name="QA_question_11">11. What should I do if Z-Roaming activation fails?</string>
    <string name="QA_question_12">12. Can I still use my physical SIM card while using the Z-Roaming service?</string>
    <string name="QA_question_13">13. Will the Z-Roaming service have any effect on the physical SIM card in the mobile phone?</string>
    <string name="QA_question_14">14. Can I ask for a refund after purchasing a Z-Roaming order?</string>
    <string name="QA_question_15">15. How do I provide feedback if I encounter any problem?</string>
    <string name="QA_question_2">2. In what countries and regions will Z-Roaming be available?</string>
    <string name="QA_question_3">3. Does Z-Roaming provide voice mails and SMS services?</string>
    <string name="QA_question_4">4. When can I purchase the Z-Roaming service?</string>
    <string name="QA_question_5">5. How do I pay for my Z-Roaming services?</string>
    <string name="QA_question_6">6. Will I be able to use the service immediately after purchasing it?</string>
    <string name="QA_question_7">7. What is the network speed for Z-Roaming?</string>
    <string name="QA_question_8">8. How long does it take to active Z-Roaming?</string>
    <string name="QA_question_9">9. Can I do hotspot sharing after activating Z-Roaming?</string>
    <string name="about_label">About Roaming Service</string>
    <string name="activate_in_deadline_prefix">Latest Enable Date</string>
    <string name="activate_in_deadline_tz">Beijing time </string>
    <string name="activate_plan">Activate</string>
    <string name="add_shortcut">Add Desktop shortcut</string>
    <string name="ali_pay">Alipay</string>
    <string name="amount">￥%1$s</string>
    <string name="app_name">Roaming Service</string>
    <string name="app_user_terms">"Roaming Service's terms of use"</string>
    <string name="attention_desc">The Z-Roaming service (hereinafter referred to as This Service) is jointly brought to you by ZUK Smartphone and Redtea Roaming. You will become a Z-Roaming service user if you agree to this Agreement and use the Z-Roaming service. Before becoming a Z-Roaming service user, please read this agreement carefully. Your use of This Service shall constitute your agreement to the entire content of this Agreement.</string>
    <string name="attention_title_1">1. Description of services</string>
    <string name="attention_title_10">10. Governing laws</string>
    <string name="attention_title_1_1">1.1 Description of product</string>
    <string name="attention_title_1_2">1.2 Scope of services</string>
    <string name="attention_title_2">2. Terms of use</string>
    <string name="attention_title_2_1">2.1 Purchase of services</string>
    <string name="attention_title_2_2">2.2 Use of services</string>
    <string name="attention_title_2_3">2.3 Service charges</string>
    <string name="attention_title_2_4">2.4 Refund on services</string>
    <string name="attention_title_3">3. Payment terms</string>
    <string name="attention_title_4">4. Extraordinary circumstances</string>
    <string name="attention_title_5">5. Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="attention_title_6">6. Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="attention_title_7">7. Limitations</string>
    <string name="attention_title_8">8. Change of terms</string>
    <string name="attention_title_9">9. Default provisions</string>
    <string name="attention_user_10">"The laws of People's Republic of China and Hong Kong SAR shall apply in enforcing, interpreting, changing, implementing and settling disputes relating to this Agreement. Disputes arising from this Agreement shall be settled through negotiations. If an agreement cannot be reached through negotiation, either party may refer the dispute to the Hong Kong International Arbitration Center."</string>
    <string name="attention_user_1_1">This Service is a network access technology jointly developed by ZUK Smartphone and Redtea Mobile. It allows its users to roam globally and enjoy fast Internet connection services without changing SIM cards. This Service has the advantages of being economical and convenient. All you have to do is purchase network access services for your required region at a service outlet.</string>
    <string name="attention_user_1_2">This service shall be gradually extended to other countries and regions with further business development.</string>
    <string name="attention_user_2_1">You can purchase services specific to your country through the integrated function while connected to a network.</string>
    <string name="attention_user_2_2">Upon successful purchase of a service, you can activate the purchased service within the specified time limit from the day of purchase. Should you fail to activate the service within the stipulated time, this service will become invalid and no refund will be made. You can activate a purchased service while your mobile phone is connected to a network. However, you will only have network connection capability within the area corresponding to the purchased service. You will also need to connect to a local roaming partner to use the service.</string>
    <string name="attention_user_2_3">Service charges (based either on duration or data usage) shall apply immediately upon successful activation of a service. Charges shall be computed continuously until the available time for the purchased service is used up.</string>
    <string name="attention_user_2_4">You can request for a refund on a purchased service before the service is activated and within its validity period.</string>
    <string name="attention_user_3">This service can be purchased by paying through WeChat Pay or Alipay while connected to a network. Hence, your device must be payment-capable in order to purchase this service.</string>
    <string name="attention_user_4">"We shall not be liable for damages of any kind arising from your failure to use this software under the circumstances listed below. These circumstances include, but are not limited to:
disruption of data transmission due to errors in the telecommunication operator’s equipment or the communication network;
disruption of services due to an event of force majeure, such as typhoons, earthquakes, power outages, floods, wars, terrorist attacks, etc.;
disruption of services due to hacker attacks;
terminal equipment failures;
absence of signals in remote areas;
absence of network coverage in areas such as subways, tunnels, basements, mountains, the sea, etc."</string>
    <string name="attention_user_5">"Should damages or compromise in user experience for other network users occur due to abuse, misuse, or wastage of or unfair advantage in data usage, the operator reserves to right to control or terminate the services provided to some users, based on the principle of fair use, where necessary. Hence, users are advised against the prolonged use of tools that incur a large amount of data usage (for online media streaming, download of videos, access of cloud files, BT online)
Attached: The principle of fair use ensures that all users enjoy the same quality of service when connecting to the Redtea Mobile network, and prevents abuse of the operator’s network and compromise in user experiences of other users."</string>
    <string name="attention_user_6">You agree to allow us to collect your location information, device ID, PLMN, LAC, CELLID and other relevant current network information during your use of the software for the purpose of enhancing the security and stability of our services. Your information may be sent to regions or countries outside of where you used our services. Under such circumstances, we will take all necessary measures to ensure the legality of such transfers, and provide suitable protection for your personal data. Your information shall only be used for purposes relating to provision of services to you.</string>
    <string name="attention_user_7">In addition to expressly accepting this terms of use and complying with relevant laws and regulations, you promise to refrain from leasing, licensing, mortgaging, translating, adjusting, changing, or modifying this service, or integrating it with other products or services; you shall not disassemble, decompile, reverse engineer or derive other products from this service, whether in whole or in part.</string>
    <string name="attention_user_8">We may modify or update this agreement from time to time, and will inform you of the changes through prominent notices. Your continued use of this software after receipt of any such notices shall constitute your consent to the changes in the agreement.</string>
    <string name="attention_user_9">For any reasonable claim arising from your use of this service under this Agreement, our compensation for the actual losses incurred by you shall not exceed the total value you paid to us for using this service.</string>
    <string name="branding_text">Redtea Mobile</string>
    <string name="button_after_pay">Finish</string>
    <string name="buy_again">Buy Again</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="cancel_order">Cancel</string>
    <string name="card_exp">Expiry date</string>
    <string name="card_hint">Credit card or bank card number</string>
    <string name="card_name">Name</string>
    <string name="card_name_hint">"Cardholder's Name"</string>
    <string name="card_pay">International Credit Card</string>
    <string name="cardno">Bank card number</string>
    <string name="checkbox_text">I agree</string>
    <string name="choose_days">%1$d day(s)</string>
    <string name="contact_bottom">Or you can add the WeChat public number for 红茶漫游 to submit your feedback</string>
    <string name="contact_info">Contact Info</string>
    <string name="copy_success">Copied successfully</string>
    <string name="current_order">Current</string>
    <string name="cvv">Security code</string>
    <string name="cvv_hint">Security code</string>
    <string name="data_miss_and_retry">Missing data. Please connect to a network and then try again</string>
    <string name="data_plan_removed">This roaming package has been under the plane.</string>
    <string name="data_plan_update_failed">Update failed and please try again later</string>
    <string name="data_plan_updated">Roaming information were updated, please read the details again before purchase.</string>
    <string name="day"> day(s)</string>
    <string name="day_formal">Day</string>
    <string name="day_short"> d(s) </string>
    <string name="default_request_server_fail">Network exception. Please try again later</string>
    <string name="description_first_launch">Overseas roaming service is a data network access service for people on a short trip. You can purchase overseas roaming services directly and enjoy network access during your overseas trip without needing to purchase a physical SIM card or renting a portable Wi-Fi device.</string>
    <string name="device_id_label">ZUK Account</string>
    <string name="dialog_exit_payment">"The payment wasn't made. Are you sure quit?"</string>
    <string name="dialog_get_imsi">Getting payment result.</string>
    <string name="dialog_prepare_pay">Payment request.</string>
    <string name="disable_fail">Closing failed</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="enable_fail">Activation failed</string>
    <string name="enable_fail_content">Failed to connect, please make sure you are in service area</string>
    <string name="enable_plan">Continue</string>
    <string name="enabling_pilot_text">This can take a few minutes, wait a moment please.</string>
    <string name="enabling_text">This can take a few minutes.</string>
    <string name="enabling_title">Activate the roaming</string>
    <string name="exp_month_hint">Month</string>
    <string name="exp_year_hint">Year</string>
    <string name="expired">Used up</string>
    <string name="failed_encrypt_card">Failed to create credit card encrypted information</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="generic_question">Frequently Asked Questions</string>
    <string name="go_pay">Pay</string>
    <string name="header_viewpager_text">%1$S ￥%2$s/day</string>
    <string name="hint_choose_day">Set the days purchased</string>
    <string name="history_order">History</string>
    <string name="hot_coverage">Popular</string>
    <string name="hour"> hour(s)</string>
    <string name="hour_short"> h(s) </string>
    <string name="in_date_suffix">Validity period</string>
    <string name="loading_neworder">Creating the order</string>
    <string name="loading_test_network">Detecting network</string>
    <string name="location_detail_title">Roaming details</string>
    <string name="location_price">￥%1$s/day</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="mcc_changed_notify_content_no_purchased_prefix">We recommend that you purchase</string>
    <string name="mcc_changed_notify_content_no_purchased_suffix">A local service. Click here to find out more.</string>
    <string name="mcc_changed_notify_content_purchased_prefix">The system detected that you have purchased</string>
    <string name="mcc_changed_notify_content_purchased_suffix">a local service. Please proceed to activate it</string>
    <string name="mcc_changed_notify_title_no_purchased">Purchase of service tip</string>
    <string name="mcc_changed_notify_title_purchased">Service activation prompt</string>
    <string name="minute"> minute(s)</string>
    <string name="minute_short"> m(s) </string>
    <string name="more_coverage">Coverage</string>
    <string name="msg_activate_plan">A SIM card slot will be used by the roaming service for data communication. The timer will start upon activation. You will not be able to use the SIM card in the occupied slot for dialing, receiving calls, and other functions. Please select the card to be occupied.</string>
    <string name="msg_cancel_order">Are you sure you want to cancel the order?</string>
    <string name="msg_enable_fail_check_area">Failed to activate roaming. Please verify that you are within the service area.</string>
    <string name="msg_enable_pilot">Your phone might not be connected to the network. In the outside, need to connect our foreign server to buy the roaming. It usually takes a few minutes, continue?</string>
    <string name="msg_enable_pilot_slot">Please select a phone card slot to connect server. It will cannot use messages and calls during the connection about ten minutes.There are no other fees incurred.</string>
    <string name="msg_refund">The refund will be returned to the account through which payment was made within 1-7 working day(s). Please contact Customer Service if you have any questions. Request for refund?</string>
    <string name="msg_warmPrompt">Your phone Wi-Fi is running on your network, roaming activation will fail. If you want to activate the roaming services, please turn off the Wi-Fi.</string>
    <string name="not_in_service_area">(Not within the service area of the package)</string>
    <string name="note_after_pay_button">You can view the details in My Roaming after clicking Finish</string>
    <string name="note_disable_plan">You can resume the use of your physical SIM card after pausing</string>
    <string name="note_disable_plan_has_info">You can resume the use of your physical SIM card(%1$s) after pausing</string>
    <string name="note_disable_plan_no_sim">You can resume the use of your physical SIM card %1$d after pausing</string>
    <string name="note_enable_plan">It will run time continuously during the service suspension.</string>
    <string name="obsolete">Expired</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="one_service_is_already_on">You are already activating another service</string>
    <string name="order_amount_desc">"Order number: %1$s
Total value of order: %2$s
Mode of payment: %3$s
ZUK Account: %4$s
Time of purchase : %5$s"</string>
    <string name="order_expired_please_purchase_again">The package has expired. Please purchase a new package</string>
    <string name="order_remain">Remaining time for the package:</string>
    <string name="payment_card_hint">International Credit Card: Visa/Mastercard/American Express</string>
    <string name="payment_ways">Payment</string>
    <string name="paymethod_alipay">Alipay</string>
    <string name="paymethod_creditcard">Credit Card</string>
    <string name="paymethod_wechat">WeChat</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="plan_enabled_notify_title_suffix">On</string>
    <string name="plan_paused_notify_title_suffix">Off</string>
    <string name="prenotify_order_expire_notification_content">Please buy another plan before expiration</string>
    <string name="prenotify_order_expire_notification_title_suffix">About 2 hours left for the service</string>
    <string name="problem_edit_hint">Please describe the problem you encountered. You will need to connect to a network to submit your entry. Should you have more than one problem please list them on separate lines to help us better identify these problems.</string>
    <string name="problem_submit_success">Thank you for your feedback. We will get in touch as soon as possible!</string>
    <string name="profile_account_hint">You can login and out ZUK Account in User Center or Setting.</string>
    <string name="provider_name">This Plan is provided by RedteaMobile</string>
    <string name="purchase">Purchase</string>
    <string name="purchase_days">Days purchased</string>
    <string name="purchase_im">Buy Now</string>
    <string name="qq">QQ</string>
    <string name="refund">Refund</string>
    <string name="refunded">Refunded</string>
    <string name="refunding">Refunding</string>
    <string name="reserved_order">Unpaid</string>
    <string name="select_sim_bottom">A SIM card slot will be used by the roaming service for data communication. You will not be able to use the SIM card in the occupied slot for dialing, receiving calls, and other functions.</string>
    <string name="select_sim_item">Card Slot %1$d (Tail number %2$s)</string>
    <string name="select_sim_item_operator">Card Slot %1$d (%2$s)</string>
    <string name="select_sim_none">Card Slot %1$d (No SIM Card)</string>
    <string name="select_slot_desc">You can change the location of the occupied card slot after stopping the roaming service</string>
    <string name="sim_slot">Card Slot %1$d</string>
    <string name="sim_slot_none">Not set</string>
    <string name="slot">slot</string>
    <string name="start_use">Start using</string>
    <string name="status_activated">Paused</string>
    <string name="status_enabled">In use</string>
    <string name="status_pause">(Paused)</string>
    <string name="status_purchased">Not activated</string>
    <string name="status_reserved">Pending payment</string>
    <string name="stop_plan_time_go_on">The plan will still count when pausing. Do you still want to pause?</string>
    <string name="store_imsi_fail">Failed to save IMSI information</string>
    <string name="str_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="string_time_left">Remaining time</string>
    <string name="submit">Send</string>
    <string name="submit_problem">submit</string>
    <string name="submit_to_cancel">Submitting</string>
    <string name="tab_home">Store</string>
    <string name="tab_order">Orders</string>
    <string name="tab_profile">Settings</string>
    <string name="text_after_pay">Successful payment</string>
    <string name="text_contact_we">Feedback</string>
    <string name="text_disable_plan">Pause</string>
    <string name="text_empty_order">No related orders</string>
    <string name="text_no_login">Not Logged In</string>
    <string name="text_payment_detail">Pay now</string>
    <string name="text_purchase_detail">Submit order</string>
    <string name="time_left">Remaining </string>
    <string name="tip_no_wechat">WeChat is not installed</string>
    <string name="tip_pay_error">Payment fails.</string>
    <string name="tip_submit_card">Submitting payment info</string>
    <string name="tip_wait_alipay_confirm">Waiting for payment confirmation</string>
    <string name="title_WarmPrompt">Warm Prompt</string>
    <string name="title_activate_plan">Activate roaming</string>
    <string name="title_afterpay">Purchased successfully</string>
    <string name="title_choose_days">Days purchased</string>
    <string name="title_creditcard_pay">International Credit Card</string>
    <string name="title_disable_plan">Pause roaming</string>
    <string name="title_enable_pilot">Connect to the server</string>
    <string name="title_enable_pilot_slot">Card slot setting</string>
    <string name="title_enabling_pilot">Attempting to connect foreign server</string>
    <string name="title_payment">Payment</string>
    <string name="title_purchase_detail">Purchase roaming</string>
    <string name="title_refund">Request a refund</string>
    <string name="title_select_slot">Occupied slot</string>
    <string name="toast_add_shortcut_failed">No permission to create a Desktop shortcut</string>
    <string name="toast_add_shortcut_succ">Add desktop shortcuts successfully</string>
    <string name="toast_check_network">Please check network connection</string>
    <string name="toast_del_order_succ">The order had been removed successfully.</string>
    <string name="toast_enablepilot_failed">Failed to connect to the server, please try again!</string>
    <string name="toast_quit_airplane">Please turn flight mode off.</string>
    <string name="total">Total</string>
    <string name="total_fee">Total</string>
    <string name="unactivated_order">Unactivated</string>
    <string name="unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="updating_data">Updating data</string>
    <string name="updating_data_plans">Roaming information is updating</string>
    <string name="user_terms">User terms</string>
    <string name="vsim_pos">Virtual SIM card slot</string>
    <string name="wechat_pay">Wechat Pay</string>
    <string name="zuk_not_login">Not logged in ZUK account</string>
    <string name="big_dot">.</string>
    <string name="contact_wechat">红茶漫游</string>
    <string name="error_400">Unexpected response code 400</string>
    <string name="number_one">1</string>
    <string name="number_two">2</string>
    <string name="semicolon">:</string>
    <string name="zero">0</string>
</resources>
